(Wyatt:)You're a grown woman,
and I respect your right
(Wyatt:)to make your own decisions,
but all I ask
(Wyatt:)is you respect me enough
to be honest about them.
(Penny:)You're right. Look, from now on,
I will tell you the truth.
(Wyatt:)Thank you. Now, why don't you go
and put some clothes on
(Wyatt:)and we'll grab a bite to eat
before I head for the airport.
(Sheldon:)- Now you.
- Daddy, he had nothing to do...
- Keep walking.
- Okay.
(Wyatt:)Please, please, please
don't give up on her.
(Leonard:)What?
(Wyatt:)I can't go back to the
skateboard idiots,
(Wyatt:)the white rappers
and all those
(Wyatt:)sweaty dumb-asses with
their backwards hats.
(Leonard:)Gee, I don't know
if it's in the cards, sir.
(Wyatt:)Then, stack the deck.
(Wyatt:)Cheat.
(Wyatt:)Lie. I don't care.
(Wyatt:)I want grandkids before I die,
(Wyatt:)and I want them to grow up
in a house without wheels.
(Leonard:)I'll give it a shot.
(Wyatt:)Thank you.
(Wyatt:)Now I'm going to do something
here to help you along.
(Leonard:)Excuse me?
Just don't panic.